that….·
What is it?
(thunder)
I see it!! Get ready to jump!!
Onyankopon!! Come quickly too!!
Not yet!! Steer right above the founder!!
After that, I'll make an emergency landing!!・
So, make sure
to descend to your ancestors!! Understood...
Onyankopon!!
Argh!!
Wow Aa!!
Tsk...!
Don't hate it.
You beast bastard!!
Saved me the trouble of searching!!
Attack target Beast Titan!!
Use all your power to destroy this!!
Stop the “earth rumbling”!!
Woooo!!
Now!!
Uuuuu...!!
Damn...!!
Ellen!!
・～
...ooooo!!
Wow!!
Shit!! I can’t get off!!
...!! Huh!! Huh!!
Woooooooooo!!
・～
liner!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuu!!
・～
(Marley soldier) To the armored giant... to the chariot giant...
That is a three-dimensional maneuvering device... No way...
Paradis Island forces are trying to stop the "earth rumbling"...
(people cheering)
liner!!
Ellen...
Let me ask you the question again .
"Where is your freedom?"
After pulling it out of there...
・～
(Sound of door creaking)
I don't think I'll be able to respond.・
If it's a hollow shell...
As expected... Sieg
hides his body in the same way as the "Warhammer Titan"...
So, out of this mountain of bones,
find a body measuring 1 meter long and 10 cm wide...
There's no way you can do that!!
So I have no choice but to give up!! Armin!!
I know!!
(Jean)!
I'll blow this place away in 1 minute!!
Cooperate with the giant of car power and get away from here!!
Armin...
I can't imagine Eren, who was expecting my attack, to die from this!!
but…·
If I blow these bones apart...
We might be able to find out where Eren and Sieg are!
(Connie) Be careful, Armin!!
(Jean) If you think something is dangerous...
Don't care about us, just give it your all!
<For those who can't throw anything away...
You won't be able to change anything.・
I know...
if I don't throw it away, nothing will change.>
< I have to give up my naive hopes ...
Eren... I...>
Armin!!
Ah!!
Struggling!! Hmmmm!!
Armin
!!
Oh!!
Let's go... Seino!
(Boy) It's not moving...
(Doctor) He's breathing...
Looks like he hit his head.
Did this man also
come from Paradis Island?
...!
Hey! Can you hear me...
Do you know Annie Leonhart?
She's my daughter!!・
Hey, you!! Can't you hear me?
It’s coming!! Reiner!!
Ooooooooo!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu !!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa…!!
Oh! What the hell are these guys?
(Jan) He's not an innocent giant...
What should I do? I'll run out of thunder spears soon.
I mean, is Armin still alive?
If he had even the slightest scratch,
he would have instantly turned into a giant...
In other words, it was captured without a scratch.・
But he was taken away by Eren's ass.
Being forced to pass by countless giants...
Even if I was in perfect condition , I wouldn't choose to attack there .
So calm down.
Hmm...!!
Mikasa, don't hurry.
Until I become a decoy and attract a group of enemies.
That's impossible, Corporal.
I found out the identity of the enemy... That's...
The ``Nine Giants'' of all time.・
I don't know if the successors still have any consciousness left,
but...
With the power of the Founding Titan, I'm sure it can be revived inexhaustibly ...
A veteran giant soldier created solely for the purpose of fighting .
There's no way we can fight against each other...
(Peak)
Yes, that's why I can't say anything leisurely.
I'm not really friends with Eren.
Eh
(Jean) Oh no way... Peak!!
Ha!!
That bastard...!
No matter how you think about it, this is the first place to shoot!!
My aim has been one from the beginning!!
hang on!!
Disappear!! Nightmare!!
Uh...｡
Peak!!
Gaaa...!! Gaaa!!
(Liner) Galliard
(Jean) This is Liner!!
Stop that movement!!
Argh!!
Corporal!!
Cuckoo...
Hurry up and get Armin
back!!
There is no other
way out!!
Otherwise, we'll all die here!!
Gaaaaa!!
(Marley soldier) Attack on Titan and Paradis Island forces
are at war...
The enemy body's path and speed remain unchanged,
heading towards us!
I can't just sit back and watch.
All members! Attack the enemy with a cannon!
Ha!!
but…! Most of the soldiers
were assigned to airship units.
There are only about three cannons that can be operated with the remaining soldiers ...
Is that
a reason to remain silent?
(Marley soldier)!
(Muller) Those people who still fight desperately on the enemy's giant back ...
What exactly are you fighting for?
Let’s go, Reiner!!
Guaaaa!!
Tee!!
Grrrr!!
Damn...!!
Raaaa!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuck!!
hurry up!!
Guaaaaaaa!!
Mikasa!!
<It was sweet...
Consciousness...
Are you trying to suffocate me like this...?
Eren... me...
No... it's that kid...
Founder Ymir.・
As Eren says,
if Eren just keeps going...
This resistance is the will of the founder Ymir...
If that's the case... Founder Ymir too...
Desires the genocide of humanity...
Founder Ymir... Invincible...
there is nothing to do….·
Like this... By the way...
Will it end... >
...!
...Bertholdt!!
Gooooooo!! Woooooo...!!
(Connie Mikasa) Liner
(Jan) Liner!!
Oi… no way…｡
Tsk!!
Huh… huh… huh…｡
Ha…ha…｡
Uuuuu!!
Wake up Connie!! Corporal!!
...Goff.
Sorry...
it looks like the three-dimensional maneuvering device has been damaged...
Me too... the handle on the right is crazy...
I can't pull it up...
Jean!! Take your hands off me!!
I can turn into a giant once more!!
So?
Will his armor be trampled by the rumbling of the earth ?
Despite its name, Teme's giant
is often broken!
(Liner) Still... Do you think you can win?
(Jan) No, but at least
let's struggle until we die.
We're the Survey Corps on the brink of death.
Oh...!
Jean...
Oh...!!
Ha...!!
Connie!!
Good...!!
Ugh...!!
Tee!!
!! Corporal!!
Woo!! Ha...!
...Cuckoo!!
come!!
I am strong!! Because!!
How much will it cost?
(Ani) Mikasa, you're a bit of a nuisance!!
Huh...
(Ani) Hold on!!
・～
No...I never
thought it would actually fly either...
It really flies...
so I had no choice but to go...
But I'm glad I came.
(Refugee) It's a bird... It's carrying people!
(Rainer) Why did you even come, Gabi?
(Gabi) It's because Reiner left us behind.
Even I can fight!!
Ani・
The Azumabit ship sank.
picture·
(Ani)
I couldn't stand Falco's transformation into a giant.・
Even though I have no proof that I can fly...
Kiyomi agreed to everything and let him go.
That's why we have to stop the rumbling!!
We have to respond to our thoughts!!
Gabi...
So aluminum...
or what about the peak?
Armin is captured by a giant and his life is in danger!
Oh!
The giant that captured Armin
should be near his tailbone.
Ani, lend me your strength!!
Your childhood friend
is being held prisoner...
Of course I'll get it back.
(Gabi) Mr. Peek
is the one with the (Liner) skull.
I tried to blow up the nape of the neck, but
I was blocked by the War Hammer Titan...
(Gabi) Explosion and
(Levi) both at the same time... Damn...
Commander・
Meanwhile, rescue Armin...
It relies on super-large explosions.
With the other hand,
aim at Eren and attack the nape of his neck.
We will divide into two groups and do it at the same time.・
There's no more time to worry about Eren
...
No... that kind of thing didn't exist from the beginning.
Commander…｡
But…｡
(Connie) But what is it?
If it hadn't been for a miracle like Falco flying,
we would have died there...
Ah... I can't accomplish anything...
Jean...
Um... what I want to say to an idiot is...
There was a lot of trouble, but... Shit!
I
don't want to give up on Eren either!! But!
Corporal can't fight anymore because of me!!
Even though the opponent is the Founding Titan!!・
What can you do if you cut back?
Mikasa...
Eren...
Let's kill Eren ...
(Ani) Mikasa...
Mikasa...
Mikasa!! You
should only think about saving Armin!!
You don't have to think about anything else
...
…Yeah.
(Marley soldiers) Oh...!
(Artillery) Oh!
Let's head towards Attack on Titan again!!
We'll do it too!!
One gate or two gates is better than nothing!!
Are you a refugee?
No, wait! ・
A faded armband mark on my left arm...!
It's Eldian!!
Oi! Wait please!!
I just came to ask you to treat the injured!!
This is far from that!
What is the real purpose?
Oh!
Mr. Leonhart That's why I said it!
I can't believe what I expect from Marleyans...!
(Eldians) Looks like we have more people here!
He also has the best experience in combat!
They have been sent to the front lines many times for the sake of the Marleyans !!
Oh...!
Put down your guns, Eldians
!!
(Eldians) Ugh...!!
(Leonhart) Come on!!
(Driver) I'm telling you to put down the gun!!
(Leonhart) Driver, before you know it...
Uh… ugh…!!
Ah...!
Damn...!
Director Mueller!!
Oh!
(gunshot)
What?
They're killing each other at a time like this!
Falco!! Be careful of flying objects!!
Oh!
(Liner) It’s coming!!
Uuuuuuuuuu!!
Jean!! Reiner!!
Please don't die!!
Ah...
you guys too...
I will attract the Warhammer Titan!!
(Liner)
Guuuuuu!! Gaaaa!!
Guaaaaaaaa!!
Guuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu...!!
Guaah!!
Now!! Jean!!
(Jean) Ugh!!
Uuuuuuu!!
Be patient!! Reiner!!・
Until I detonate it...
Damn...!
That's normal, it increases me...!
(Peak) Heeeeeeee!!
I wish I could do three-dimensional maneuvers too...!
Shit, don't come closer... Gah!! Ugh!!
...Peak!! No!! Run away!!
Jean... I'm
not cut out for battle.
I thought it was a giant working on chores ...
It's a mistake!!
(Peak)
As long as I don't get killed, the sustaining power of the car is...
I can fight until I win!!
Even hundreds of times!!
That's why Jean!! Don't worry about me and
detonate!!
Argh!!
Well, even if I win a hundred times...
If there are a million enemies, there's nothing you can do...
Goaaaaaa!!
Gooooo!!
Ha ha ha ha...!
(Ani) Even Bertolt is a puppet...
can not forgive…!
…there was!!
that! A pig or some kind of giant!!
Which/
that! Over there... that!
(Ani)
Where? What are the nine giants?
Is it a Kuruma force? A beast? It might be a jaw!!
(Ani)...I don't know!!
Mikasa!! You're being serious!!
You're doing it!!
Ah!! Only one escaped!!
(Ani) That... That's an okapi!!
I don't know about okapi!!
(Ani) Go Falco!!
Chase that okapi or something to the tailbone.
Bring back Armin!!
I can support you with this rifle!
There are no giants here who would die because of it.
(Levi)
<Where is Sieg? Where is he?
Damn... Even if I find it,
it's still this crap.
It's a hindrance... Shit...!!>
<I have never failed to follow his orders
...not even once...
But... why is his last command the only one...>
<Our role
may have ended there...
If the role was just to deliver the kids to the sea ...>
<No...
The world without giants that we dreamed of...
It must have been a shockingly auspicious
ideal world.・
Otherwise,
it's not worth their hearts.・
Erwin I...
I have no regrets about not choosing you.>
・～
Tae!! Connie! I went there!!
Wait, Oi!!
It’s gone!! You can run towards the skull!!
Ani!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuck!!
Oh!!
Stop, Okapi!!
Ha...!
Aaah!!
Ugh...!
...
Aaaaaa!!
Uuuuuuu!!
Ani!!
It's no good if you're alone!!
You'll be killed right away!!
For those with super large okapi...!!
Unpalatable…!
…Oi!!
Why...
why isn't my body moving...
Please move!
Everyone will die!
Liner...Peak...
Jean... Connie...
Mikasa... Ani.
Everyone is going to die!!
Wake up, you scum!!
Bastard!! Useless!!
Ugh... huh...
I hate myself! Zuuutt you!!
You have been betraying me!!
The life I received!! The expectations!! The responsibility too!!
Nothing!! Nothing!!
You couldn't give anything back!!
But!! Why is he dead?
Move!! Move!!
Aaaaaaa…!!
Aaaaaaa...!!
(People scream)
・～
(cry)
teeth….
・～
<Sand…｡・
Think about it...
if you're really dead...
How can you think without oxygen flowing to your brain ? >
<This is
not a dream, a vision, or an afterlife.>
<This is the “road”…
This is... reality!!>
<I'm supposed to be in the giant's mouth, so
why do I know everyone's situation...? ・
Is it because all Eldians
are connected through "roads"? ・
Then
maybe we can do something here...>
Yes, think about it...
Think!!
picture….
(Armin's footsteps)
Hello,
Mr. Zeke.
Ellen's friend.
Were you also
eaten by Ymir?
(Jeek) A long time ago...
When only matter existed in this world ...
(Jeek) Something imaginable and intangible
repeatedly appears and disappears.
Eventually, something survived.
It's called "life."
The reason why life remained in the end was...
This is because life
has the property of ``multiplying. ''
In order to increase, life changes its shape.
We have adapted to any environment and
have become what we are today.
More, wider, richer...
In other words, the purpose of life is to "increase."
This sand, stones, and water
are not going to increase.
However, life is still desperately trying to increase.
After all, death and species extinction go against the purpose of increasing numbers.
For that reason, there is a penalty called fear.
That child
was also desperately trying to escape from that pain...
Create a stronger, larger, and immortal body.
And to a world where even death doesn't exist...
She escaped...
That's the founder Ymir...
this is the "world where death doesn't exist"...
If that's the case,
what exactly is Ymir's purpose?
I also spend a lot of time here ...
I tried to understand her .
Even though I have this much power ...
I couldn't go against King Fritz
...
Stayed here for 2000 years
The reason I continued to follow King Fritz.
I'm sure I left something to be desired,
but...
Eren understood that, but
I couldn't...
That's why Ymir
joined Eren.
Please tell me
how to return to the outside world from here.
Well... I don't think it's possible anymore...
I'm not giving up on anything.
Why...
eh... That's...
Is it because it will still increase?
Is it really that important to you to keep the species alive ?
What's happening now...
This can be described as a tragic state of life ruled by fear .
brought about by completely meaningless
life activities.
Don't be afraid...
my friends are fighting!!
Because now we can still save many people
from fear...!!
I am fighting fear!!
Why can't I lose...?
Being alive means
you'll die someday, right?
Hmm…｡
Maybe I'll feel relieved before it's all over ...
I don't even know what it means...
After the days of being forced to dance just to increase ...
Now I'm free...
ah….
It was dusk, facing a tree on the hill...
The three of us raced...
Eren, who had just
started talking, suddenly started running...
Mikasa dared to run behind Eren...
I'm the dobe after all...
But... that day, the wind was warm and
it felt good just running...
There were a lot of dry leaves.
At that time, for some reason, I thought...
I think the three of us were born to play here together ...
Even when I'm reading a book at home on a rainy day...
Even when the squirrel ate the fruit I gave it...
That's what I thought when we all walked through the market...
I feel like this ordinary moment is so important...
it is…?
Hmm…｡
This one was buried in sand...
Why is that...
Now... But for me, this is...
It's not necessary or anything to increase
...
It's something very
important.
Ah... that's right.
Just throw it and catch it...
Throw it again. Just repeat it.
It doesn't make any sense...but it's true...
I
was happy just playing catch the whole time.
・
Peek!! Peak!!
Gah...!
If my arm heals,
I can still fight...!
It's the limit!! Back up to the bottom of the liner!
(Peak) is...!!
Liner!!
Oh...! ・
Jean!! Peak!!
Woo!!
Ani!!
Woo... woo...!
Coo...!
...!!
Ha, what...
Ugh... ugh...! ・
Porco!! Marcel!!
・
(Liner) Ymir!!
Did you help me...
B...Bertholdt...
I don't know...but...
Don't miss this opportunity!!
I got it!!
Armin!!
Give it back!!!
...Gaha!
Armin!!
Damn!!
Oooooooooooooooo!!
Ugh!!
Ani!!
Goho goho geho…｡
Kaha… gehogeho… ugh…｡
Annie...
Armin...
Sorry everyone...
But... it's okay now.
(Connie) Ani!! It’s behind you!!
・～
・
(Gabi) What do you mean?
A giant is helping you?
It seems so.
(Jeek) Ooi!!
Ooooo!!
...!!
Here it is!!
Eh...
that's stupid...
You wanted to meet me, right? Levi!!
I didn't want to meet you though!!
...Sieg.
(encourage)
(Connie) What's going on? This is...
It's all thanks to Sieg.
Sieg...
It awakened everyone who had been sleeping in the world of the road, where there is no life or death .
All Eldians
are connected by "roads".
That's probably...
This is because Founder Ymir
is seeking a connection.
Asking us something...
...!
Bertolt...
Kusava-san,
our wishes didn't come true...
I still think that the euthanasia plan was not a mistake...
But
if it's just to play catch with you...
I wonder if I can be born again...
that's why…·
I'd like to thank you, Dad.
I
took everything from you.
Life, power, and precious memories...
That's why I understand.
I can't stay still here .
everyone….
(Zeek Armin) Lend me your strength.
・～
Isn't it nice weather...
I wish I had thought of that sooner...
Well...
The bugs are too good to kill so many of them
...
The rumbling... has stopped...
Uaaaaaaa!!
Go!! Jean!!
Nu!! Argh!!
(Jean) Uuuuuuu!!
(Peak) Jean!!
Oh!!
this…!!
Hurrying to death... you stupid idiot!!
(explosion sound)
Argh!!
Grrrr…!!!!
This guy!! On Eren’s neck again!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuck!!
Liner!!
(Connie) Jean!! Peak!!・
Hurry and leave!!
Armin will blow away every bone!!
Wait!! Liner!!
(Peak) If it's an armored giant,
I'm sure it can withstand a super-sized explosion.
Above all, letting this opportunity pass
would mean ruining Reiner's resolve.
Nuaaaaaaaa!!!
thank you….
Without everyone's help...
I couldn't stop the rumbling...
Goodbye...
Eren.
(explosion sound)
Ugh...
(Gabi's father) Sister!! Are you okay?
What on earth...
・It was a huge explosion!!
・Did everyone survive?
(Father Falco)! that…!
(Jean) Look at the bones...!!・
Is Eren... dead?
Ugh!!
Ackerman awakens to his power...
Apparently , sudden headaches were
common...
I've been a slave who just follows orders...
ever since I was a kid...
Mikasa, I hated you.
Oh!
Oh...!!
・～
(Connie) That doesn't mean I don't have any regrets.・
but…·
We weren't wrong.
We stopped the rumbling...
How... from the containment area to here...
(Carina) Leonhart-
san led everyone to this point.
Let me go.
…Ha!
Armin!!
Where is Liner?
(Gabi) Reiner!!
(Jan) You're safe!!
Oi!! Look!! Over there!!
Are you still alive after that explosion?
Yes... what on earth is that?
Well...just...
It certainly shouldn't be kept alive.
(Explosion sound)
(Aluminum liner)!!
(explosion sound)
Well... I guess...
I don't think you'll die from that.
Ah...but what should I do?
...Eren.
(Earth rumbling)
That's bad!! If Eren comes into contact with the glowing thing,
the ground might start rumbling again...!!
(Connie) Oh, I have to kill him!!
How do you kill someone who survived that explosion?
The person you should aim for is Eren.
You understand...
this nightmare won't end until we kill him...
Dad, there's one last job left.
I'll do it for you, brother.
…why?
Why...
why does this happen?
Hah...
Did you hurt your leg?
Oh!
No, it was bad from the beginning...I was saved.
Can you walk?
(Leonhart)
If you hadn't shot all the bullets into the air...
We
would still be killing each other...
I've made enough mistakes...
Let 's work together
to get through this.Ah
...
(Ani) Dad
!!
Ha ha ha...
A...Ani?
(Gabi) This smoke is coming from that glowing thing!!
Did you die?
No... it smells like a dead giant.
Oh! this is…·
It's the same method as Ragako Village...
Oh!
…picture?
Mikasa!! Peak!! Get on Falco!!
Get out of here!!
What... what are you talking about?
Ackerman and those with the power of the Titans
are exceptions.
You should know best what to do !
That's... that's too much.
hurry up!!
No!! Dad!! Dad!!
Guaaaaaaaaaaaa...!!
Is this our last moment?
Well…｡・
I'll leave the rest to my friends,
because that's the end of the Survey Corps.
Do you remember, Jean? ・
About the night I burned the corpse.Ah
...
(Connie) It's all your fault, isn't it? ・
We were forced to save humanity...
Oh...!!
Idiot...
Is there something so... stupid like this?
(Onyankopon) Oi!! Oi!! Ani!!
Are you okay? What the hell happened?
(Roaring)
!!
Hey... Secretary!!
Ah...!!
Ugh...!
This guy...he called for the soldiers...
Just kidding!!
Never pass here!!
Wow!! Guooooo!!
Damn...! You really
like hell, Eren!!
It's okay... I
'll be with you till the end!!!
WOOOOOOOO!!
Connie... Jean... Gabi...!!
No way... why, mother...
Uggaaaa!!
(Liner)
Peak!! Ani!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu!!
(Liner) We are...
How can I be rewarded?
Daaaa!! Uuuuu!!
(Levi) Mikasa・
Stay strong!!
We are the only ones who can kill Eren now!!
Ugh...!!
No more... no more...
Intolerable…!
I want to go home…!
I want to go back to our house...
Mikasa... wake up.
yeah….
I'm going to catch a cold.
Eren...?
that? I….
When did you fall asleep...
(Sound of chopping firewood)
I must have been really tired...
hmm...
I feel like I was having a long dream...
Let's just relax and do nothing today
.
I also managed to catch a big fish...
Mikasa...
Why are you crying?
…picture?
Why is that?
I... I wonder if it's okay to stay here ...
There's nothing I can do anymore...
picture?
Since that day when we left everything behind and
ran away here...
Two months have passed since Marley's war ended...
The war of invasion of Paradis Island is about to begin...
If we don't run, we'll all be killed...
Armin
is probably desperately looking for us too.
I have the ability to send Historia to hell and
kill each other for eternity.
Nor could they massacre people outside the island
...
In that case,
let's live the remaining four years of our lives quietly...
Just the two of us in a place where no one is around...
Mikasa, you were the one who said that .
Yeah….
I'm sorry...
I promised not to talk about this...
Can I make another promise?
If I die, please
throw away this muffler...
You're going to live a long time from now on...
Please forget about me and be free...
Please, Mikasa...
Forget it.
・～
sorry.
Can not.
Eren is in your mouth!!
Everyone cooperate!!
(Levi) Understood, Mikasa!!
(Falco) Oooooooo!!
Ellen!!!
Damn...!!
Dah!!
!! Doaaaa!!
Tee!!
・～
Take care.
Ellen.
・～
I know it 's for the sake of the future seen through the power of Attack on Titan,
but...
The reason you had to beat me up ...what?
Was it necessary to throw in a knee kick?
Desperate to push you away...
Even I was wondering what I was doing
...
Leave it to the momentum and flow...
It was really bad...
You should tell Mikasa that, not me.
You hurt me by saying such bullshit...
Ah... that's right.
Everything is
about us who were pushed away...
Defeat Eren
To make him into a hero who saved humanity from extinction ?
That's it.
You will be the benefactors of all surviving humans .
Although he was the "Island Devil",
he disobeyed Paradis Island and stuck to humanity.
He must become the most respected person in this world .
Well then,
like the Tiber family after the Great War...
Are you telling me to protect Paradis Island from the retaliation of humans outside the wall ?
There's no way we
can become heroes...
It's unfortunate, but me and everyone...
I'm not going to play the hero the way you want me to .
where….
That's where we wanted to go.
Let's talk while walking.
The story of the founder Ymir...
(Eren Armin) Haa...!
This is flaming water...
It really flows like a river...
How far
did you talk?
picture?
Because the founder Ymir has been following King Fritz for 2,000 years ...
The power of the Titans still exists...
That's right... My hometown was burned down, my parents were killed, and
my tongue was pulled out...
Even after gaining power equal to that of God,
he remained obedient...
I wonder what made her do that...
I touched her on the "road" and felt...
I couldn't believe it, but...
The founder Ymir... loved King Fritz.
…picture?
This is the true identity of what has continued to bind Ymir even after 2000 years .
It is impossible to understand the depths of founder Ymir's heart .
But... she was definitely in pain.
For 2,000 years,
I've been searching for someone to free me from my suffering...
It finally appeared.
That's Mikasa.
...Eh... I said Mikasa...
I said it. I guess you didn't hear me...
I heard you!
Why... Mikasa?
Well...
only the founder Ymir can understand...
I still
don't know what Mikasa will do...
What I knew for sure
was the result of Mikasa...
I kept going just to reach that result ...
Massacre humanity and
make them kill each other on Paradis Island.
Everyone... my precious friends...
I went into battle without knowing if I would survive .
That's the future I saw at the medal award ceremony...
Armin...
My head
is messed up...
The influence of the founder's power is...
There is no past and no future, they exist at the same time...
So... I had no choice...
That day... that time...
Bertholdt
shouldn't have died yet...
…picture?
So I missed it...
What led me to...
Let's go, Ellen.
…Ahh.
So... what were you thinking?
what?
It's about Mikasa.
Do you think you can forget about Eren and
live happily with someone else?
As you wish.
Well, I don't know.
Good...! Huh… hah…!
Ha... ha...｡
...It hurts.
You don't understand,
I don't remember forgiving you!!
What do you think about Mikasa's love for you
?
To Mikasa, who has risked her life
to only look at Eren...
Do you think you can just forget about me ?
At least Mikasa
can forget about making this woman cry...
You should be happy!!
Well, I feel like I'll be able to find a good person sooner than I expected and get along easily...
No...
Huh?
I don't want that!! I
can't believe Mikasa has a man!!
I want you to think only of me for the rest of your life!!
Even after I die...
I hope it lasts for more than 10 years!!
Huh… eh…｡
Ah... that's right...
To say something so... uncool...
Please don't tell Mikasa about this...
I want you to be happy... really...
But… ah…｡
Damn it...!
I don't want to die...
I want to be with Mikasa and everyone...
Ellen! Let's search without giving up!!
Isn't there another way...!
No!!
I'm sure everyone , just like me,
didn't want to die...
But... I...
...!
It's 80%
...huh?
They trampled 80% of humanity to death...
What a...
thing...!!
Eren!! Why!!
I am literally
trying to complete the eradication of humanity outside the wall.
You will be blocked.
The result is 80%...
The world outside the wall
will fall to the same level of civilization as Paradis Island.
In other words... it probably won't be a unilateral war of retaliation
...
This fight will never end.
Huh, hah, hah...
What is that...
Are you trying to say that what we did was in vain?
That's okay!!
Stop the massacre that hasn't happened yet!!
You can't...
you can save up to 20% of humanity.
It's already decided...
Has it been decided...?
You decided to kill yourself, right?
I've tried so many times and been disappointed, but ...
The memories of the future
will remain exactly the same...
Armin... as you said...
I am...a free slave.
Uh… ugh…!
What a stupid thing!!
It's already...!! Is there no way to take it back?
This is impossible!!
This is not a solution!!
There would be no war without people...
Is there anyone who would take such a joke seriously?
Ellen...
It's true that this battle has no end in sight...
The hell we experienced
was repeated over and over again...I'm sure...
Still...someday...
I'm sure someday
we'll understand each other...
Even a small wish ...
No one believes me anymore...
The only lesson left is...
kill or be killed... That's it...
Are you saying that you did everything for us ?
(Grisha) "Eren"... That's your name.
No, that's not true...
Eren... you're free...
I... I wanted it to be flat...
I wanted to see this view...
…why?
I don't know why, but...
I wanted to do it... I really wanted to...
I thought it was all to protect you ...
But... Sasha and Hanji both
died because of me.
I ended up having them kill each other with Flock and the others
...
Why... why did this happen...
I finally understood.
It's because you're an idiot.
An ordinary idiot who can be found anywhere
has acquired power...
That's why I couldn't help but end up like this ...
Isn't that what it means?
I understand...
!
I have also had times when I wanted to erase people from this world .
Liar...
that's why you think that...
No one would think so.
Because he is a hero who saved 20% of humanity...
But... I was the one who showed Ellen the books about the outside world .
I was the one who made Eren imagine a free world without anyone .
it is?
I guess you finally noticed...
even though it was always there at your feet...
Because I'm always looking far away...
Thank you Ellen.
You showed me this scenery on the other side of the wall ...
This is what we did.
So... from now on, we'll be together forever...
from now? …where?
If only... in hell.
I will suffer for the crime of killing 80% of humanity .
Two people.
・～
Armin... it's time.
I'll erase the memories I spent here...
I'll remember it again when it's all over...
Ah... next time we'll kill each other...
And the next time we meet...
Ahh….
I'll be waiting for you... in hell.
Yeah….
We'll be together forever...
(Ani) Has your injury healed yet?
that…? Annie...?
Yeah...because I had time.
I remembered... this...
...Armin
!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...!!
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...!!
Armin also regained his memory, right?
When Ellen came to see us...
Ah... I heard...
The result of Mikasa's choices...
The power of the Titans
will be erased from this world...
I remember... you polite idiot.
Eren... you're that guy...
Eren says...
Mom said she'll turn back into a human too...
He...
told us... to live long...
Are you...?
It's an unnecessary burden for you, you
bastard who is in a hurry to die...
yes….
I wanted to talk to you too...
welcome home.
Right now... Dad.
Gabbyiiiiii!!
Hey you guys.
Were you watching?
This seems to be the ending.
You all gave... your heart...
・～
(Connie) Sasha…｡
father, mother…!
Ah... Gabi...｡
(Falco) Gabiiii!!
Gabbyiiiiii!!
Falco!!
・～
mother….
I...
it's like I'm not an armored giant anymore...
(Karina)
...Is it true?
That was good...
!
I'm sorry for all this time... Reiner...
I didn't need anything more .
Oh...!
Already... let's go.
picture…? where?
If I stay here like this, Eren will surely...
I can't give him a proper burial.
…I agree.
Let me sleep in a quiet place...
Eren always fell asleep there.
Yes, I think it's a good place.
・～
(Leon Hart) Listen, Secretary Mueller!
Eren Jaeger is dead!
Even the power of the giant disappeared from this world...! ・
We are just people now!
Can you prove it? Now here.
If it's a blood test...
(Muller) Right here and now!!
Please... prove it.・
Is it a human... or a giant...
If we still have the power of the Titans,
we will use our strength to resist.
However, even now that a gun is pointed at you,
you remain helpless...
This is proof that we are human beings.
you…?
Armin Arlert, Eldian of Paradis Island .
He is the one who killed Eren Jaeger from Attack on Titan .
It was you...
The one who was looking inside my head...
I think your love was a long nightmare...
The lives that were taken will never come back.
nevertheless…·
I exist because you created a life for me .
・～
Good night, Ymir.
(Histria) <Three years have passed since that day, which was called the "Battle of Heaven and Earth"
...
An incredible number of lives have been taken.
Those who survived
may also suffer from scars that never heal.
<As the world in the midst of loss fears,
the country of Eldia...
Formed an "army" controlled by the Jaeger faction .
I am getting stronger day by day.・
Fearing retribution from the surviving humans on the other side of the ocean ...
The island will come together and raise its voice.・
If you win, you live; if you lose, you die.・
if you do not fight, you can not win.·
Fight, fight.・
Even if the giants disappear,
the conflict will not end.・
Eren
told me about the future as far as he knew.
Even if I can't see any further into the future ...
I could clearly see this future .・
I'm sure this result
wasn't just Eren's choice.・
This world is the result of our choices .
We have to fight.・
In order not to fight any more...
Even if I have to live my days without peace again .・
It's not the life he wanted for us ...
Whether he wanted it or not,
it was entrusted to us.・
How to live the remaining grace...>
"A world without giants."
No matter how many times I look at it, Historia's handwriting is beautiful.
It also smells good...
(Jan) I've said it many times, but
stop feeling bad about married people. It's disgusting.
It seems like Jean is worried about his hair and
can't help it.
Who are you going to show it to?
For female students reading history textbooks.
Are you confusing this with a picture book about horses?
(Jan)
It's a shame that your lifespan has been extended, Reiner.
・(Sound of door opening)
Paradis Island is now in sight.
Armin: Do you really think it'll work out?
Destroy the wall, betray the island...
The people who killed Eren, who are worshiped by the people of Eldia ...
Serving as ambassador for the Allied powers in peace negotiations...
I don't think I would be surprised if it was sunk around here
...
Ah... I can't believe the ship is still
floating...
This is the role of the world's hero that that idiot forced upon me .
What do you want to live longer?
What, Annie , did you just board the ship with the intention of returning home alive ?
No way, but you guys...
You didn't come here to commit suicide,
right?
The answer is that I'm headed to hell again .
The Survey Corps
are dreamers and don't give up easily.
I'm a military police officer.
For now, I'm not killed yet.
Everyone on Paradis Island
should want to know.
Our story.
・～
People who killed each other a lot...
Why did it appear on Paradis Island...
Are you appealing for peace?
・～
The story we saw...
Let's talk about it all.
・～
Ellen... everyone will be coming to see you soon.
Are you happy?
・～
Huh… ugh…｡
Uh... huh...｡
Huh... uh...｡
Huh... huh...｡
(cry)
I want to see you again….
(Sound of wings)
!!
・～
Ellen...
Thank you for wrapping the muffler...
・～
・“Time brought [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]
Calm days [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]”
・"Like a flower in your hand [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]"
・"Hidden words [Out: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]
die without telling anyone [Out: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]"
≪Requiem of the night that repeats≫
・" The flowers you loved on the coffin "
・"If you want to forgive your sins,
let the dawn shine"
・“Be fruitful and multiply,
fill the earth”
・`` I released the steel bird into the sky.''
・“Freedom
becomes a crimson bow and arrow.”
・"Repeat over and over again"
・“ I can’t throw away the stone I was throwing back .”
・"The sky that cowardly humans looked up at"
・"A bow and arrow of the underworld that resembles a meteor"
・"History repeats itself"
・“And then it becomes ≪Nothing≫ again.”
・"Can you hear me? Get out of here [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]"
・“No matter how many times I get lost [Outside:9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]”
・"Plants have sprouted even in the burnt out fields."
・"The shadow and light of civilization"
・"In the cave of the great tree where I watched everything"
・"What do you know?"