that….·
What is it?
(thunder)
I see it!! Get ready to jump!!
Onyankopon!! Come quickly too!!
Not yet!! Steer right above the founder!!
After that, I'll make an emergency landing!!・
So, make sure
to descend to your ancestors!! Understood...
Onyankopon!!
Argh!!
Wow Aa!!
Tsk...!
Don't hate it.
You beast bastard!!
Saved me the trouble of searching!!
Attack target Beast Titan!!
Use all your power to destroy this!!
Stop the “earth rumbling”!!
Woooo!!
Now!!
Uuuuu...!!
Damn...!!
Ellen!!
・～
...ooooo!!
Wow!!
Shit!! I can’t get off!!
...!! Huh!! Huh!!
Woooooooooo!!
・～
liner!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuu!!
・～
(Marley soldier) To the armored giant... to the chariot giant...
That is a three-dimensional maneuvering device... No way...
Paradis Island forces are trying to stop the "earth rumbling"...
(people cheering)
liner!!
Ellen...
Let me ask you the question again .
"Where is your freedom?"
After pulling it out of there...
・～
(Sound of door creaking)
I don't think I'll be able to respond.・
If it's a hollow shell...
As expected... Sieg
hides his body in the same way as the "Warhammer Titan"...
So, out of this mountain of bones,
find a body measuring 1 meter long and 10 cm wide...
There's no way you can do that!!
So I have no choice but to give up!! Armin!!
I know!!
(Jean)!
I'll blow this place away in 1 minute!!
Cooperate with the giant of car power and get away from here!!
Armin...
I can't imagine Eren, who was expecting my attack, to die from this!!
but…·
If I blow these bones apart...
We might be able to find out where Eren and Sieg are!
(Connie) Be careful, Armin!!
(Jean) If you think something is dangerous...
Don't care about us, just give it your all!
<For those who can't throw anything away...
You won't be able to change anything.・
I know...
if I don't throw it away, nothing will change.>
< I have to give up my naive hopes ...
Eren... I...>
Armin!!
Ah!!
Struggling!! Hmmmm!!
Armin
!!
Oh!!
Let's go... Seino!
(Boy) It's not moving...
(Doctor) He's breathing...
Looks like he hit his head.
Did this man also
come from Paradis Island?
...!
Hey! Can you hear me...
Do you know Annie Leonhart?
She's my daughter!!・
Hey, you!! Can't you hear me?
It’s coming!! Reiner!!
Ooooooooo!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu !!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa…!!
Oh! What the hell are these guys?
(Jan) He's not an innocent giant...
What should I do? I'll run out of thunder spears soon.
I mean, is Armin still alive?
If he had even the slightest scratch,
he would have instantly turned into a giant...
In other words, it was captured without a scratch.・
But he was taken away by Eren's ass.
Being forced to pass by countless giants...
Even if I was in perfect condition , I wouldn't choose to attack there .
So calm down.
Hmm...!!
Mikasa, don't hurry.
Until I become a decoy and attract a group of enemies.
That's impossible, Corporal.
I found out the identity of the enemy... That's...
The ``Nine Giants'' of all time.・
I don't know if the successors still have any consciousness left,
but...
With the power of the Founding Titan, I'm sure it can be revived inexhaustibly ...
A veteran giant soldier created solely for the purpose of fighting .
There's no way we can fight against each other...
(Peak)
Yes, that's why I can't say anything leisurely.
I'm not really friends with Eren.
Eh
(Jean) Oh no way... Peak!!
Ha!!
That bastard...!
No matter how you think about it, this is the first place to shoot!!
My aim has been one from the beginning!!
hang on!!
Disappear!! Nightmare!!
Uh...｡
Peak!!
Gaaa...!! Gaaa!!
(Liner) Galliard
(Jean) This is Liner!!
Stop that movement!!
Argh!!
Corporal!!
Cuckoo...
Hurry up and get Armin
back!!
There is no other
way out!!
Otherwise, we'll all die here!!
Gaaaaa!!
(Marley soldier) Attack on Titan and Paradis Island forces
are at war...
The enemy body's path and speed remain unchanged,
heading towards us!
I can't just sit back and watch.
All members! Attack the enemy with a cannon!
Ha!!
but…! Most of the soldiers
were assigned to airship units.
There are only about three cannons that can be operated with the remaining soldiers ...
Is that
a reason to remain silent?
(Marley soldier)!
(Muller) Those people who still fight desperately on the enemy's giant back ...
What exactly are you fighting for?
Let’s go, Reiner!!
Guaaaa!!
Tee!!
Grrrr!!
Damn...!!
Raaaa!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuck!!
hurry up!!
Guaaaaaaa!!
Mikasa!!
<It was sweet...
Consciousness...
Are you trying to suffocate me like this...?
Eren... me...
No... it's that kid...
Founder Ymir.・
As Eren says,
if Eren just keeps going...
This resistance is the will of the founder Ymir...
If that's the case... Founder Ymir too...
Desires the genocide of humanity...
Founder Ymir... Invincible...
there is nothing to do….·
Like this... By the way...
Will it end... >
...!
...Bertholdt!!
Gooooooo!! Woooooo...!!
(Connie Mikasa) Liner
(Jan) Liner!!
Oi… no way…｡
Tsk!!
Huh… huh… huh…｡
Ha…ha…｡
Uuuuu!!
Wake up Connie!! Corporal!!
...Goff.
Sorry...
it looks like the three-dimensional maneuvering device has been damaged...
Me too... the handle on the right is crazy...
I can't pull it up...
Jean!! Take your hands off me!!
I can turn into a giant once more!!
So?
Will his armor be trampled by the rumbling of the earth ?
Despite its name, Teme's giant
is often broken!
(Liner) Still... Do you think you can win?
(Jan) No, but at least
let's struggle until we die.
We're the Survey Corps on the brink of death.
Oh...!
Jean...
Oh...!!
Ha...!!
Connie!!
Good...!!
Ugh...!!
Tee!!
!! Corporal!!
Woo!! Ha...!
...Cuckoo!!
come!!
I am strong!! Because!!
How much will it cost?
(Ani) Mikasa, you're a bit of a nuisance!!
Huh...
(Ani) Hold on!!
・～
No...I never
thought it would actually fly either...
It really flies...
so I had no choice but to go...
But I'm glad I came.
(Refugee) It's a bird... It's carrying people!
(Rainer) Why did you even come, Gabi?
(Gabi) It's because Reiner left us behind.
Even I can fight!!
Ani・
The Azumabit ship sank.
picture·
(Ani)
I couldn't stand Falco's transformation into a giant.・
Even though I have no proof that I can fly...
Kiyomi agreed to everything and let him go.
That's why we have to stop the rumbling!!
We have to respond to our thoughts!!
Gabi...
So aluminum...
or what about the peak?
Armin is captured by a giant and his life is in danger!
Oh!
The giant that captured Armin
should be near his tailbone.
Ani, lend me your strength!!
Your childhood friend
is being held prisoner...
Of course I'll get it back.
(Gabi) Mr. Peek
is the one with the (Liner) skull.
I tried to blow up the nape of the neck, but
I was blocked by the War Hammer Titan...
(Gabi) Explosion and
(Levi) both at the same time... Damn...
Commander・
Meanwhile, rescue Armin...
It relies on super-large explosions.
With the other hand,
aim at Eren and attack the nape of his neck.
We will divide into two groups and do it at the same time.・
There's no more time to worry about Eren
...
No... that kind of thing didn't exist from the beginning.
Commander…｡
But…｡
(Connie) But what is it?
If it hadn't been for a miracle like Falco flying,
we would have died there...
Ah... I can't accomplish anything...
Jean...
Um... what I want to say to an idiot is...
There was a lot of trouble, but... Shit!
I
don't want to give up on Eren either!! But!
Corporal can't fight anymore because of me!!
Even though the opponent is the Founding Titan!!・
What can you do if you cut back?
Mikasa...
Eren...
Let's kill Eren ...
(Ani) Mikasa...
Mikasa...
Mikasa!! You
should only think about saving Armin!!
You don't have to think about anything else
...
…Yeah.
(Marley soldiers) Oh...!
(Artillery) Oh!
Let's head towards Attack on Titan again!!
We'll do it too!!
One gate or two gates is better than nothing!!
Are you a refugee?
No, wait! ・
A faded armband mark on my left arm...!
It's Eldian!!
Oi! Wait please!!
I just came to ask you to treat the injured!!
This is far from that!
What is the real purpose?
Oh!
Mr. Leonhart That's why I said it!
I can't believe what I expect from Marleyans...!
(Eldians) Looks like we have more people here!
He also has the best experience in combat!
They have been sent to the front lines many times for the sake of the Marleyans !!
Oh...!
Put down your guns, Eldians
!!
(Eldians) Ugh...!!
(Leonhart) Come on!!
(Driver) I'm telling you to put down the gun!!
(Leonhart) Driver, before you know it...
Uh… ugh…!!
Ah...!
Damn...!
Director Mueller!!
Oh!
(gunshot)
What?
They're killing each other at a time like this!
Falco!! Be careful of flying objects!!
Oh!
(Liner) It’s coming!!
Uuuuuuuuuu!!
Jean!! Reiner!!
Please don't die!!
Ah...
you guys too...
I will attract the Warhammer Titan!!
(Liner)
Guuuuuu!! Gaaaa!!
Guaaaaaaaa!!
Guuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu...!!
Guaah!!
Now!! Jean!!
(Jean) Ugh!!
Uuuuuuu!!
Be patient!! Reiner!!・
Until I detonate it...
Damn...!
That's normal, it increases me...!
(Peak) Heeeeeeee!!
I wish I could do three-dimensional maneuvers too...!
Shit, don't come closer... Gah!! Ugh!!
...Peak!! No!! Run away!!
Jean... I'm
not cut out for battle.
I thought it was a giant working on chores ...
It's a mistake!!
(Peak)
As long as I don't get killed, the sustaining power of the car is...
I can fight until I win!!
Even hundreds of times!!
That's why Jean!! Don't worry about me and
detonate!!
Argh!!
Well, even if I win a hundred times...
If there are a million enemies, there's nothing you can do...
Goaaaaaa!!
Gooooo!!
Ha ha ha ha...!
(Ani) Even Bertolt is a puppet...
can not forgive…!
…there was!!
that! A pig or some kind of giant!!
Which/
that! Over there... that!
(Ani)
Where? What are the nine giants?
Is it a Kuruma force? A beast? It might be a jaw!!
(Ani)...I don't know!!
Mikasa!! You're being serious!!
You're doing it!!
Ah!! Only one escaped!!
(Ani) That... That's an okapi!!
I don't know about okapi!!
(Ani) Go Falco!!
Chase that okapi or something to the tailbone.
Bring back Armin!!
I can support you with this rifle!
There are no giants here who would die because of it.
(Levi)
<Where is Sieg? Where is he?
Damn... Even if I find it,
it's still this crap.
It's a hindrance... Shit...!!>
<I have never failed to follow his orders
...not even once...
But... why is his last command the only one...>
<Our role
may have ended there...
If the role was just to deliver the kids to the sea ...>
<No...
The world without giants that we dreamed of...
It must have been a shockingly auspicious
ideal world.・
Otherwise,
it's not worth their hearts.・
Erwin I...
I have no regrets about not choosing you.>
・～
Tae!! Connie! I went there!!
Wait, Oi!!
It’s gone!! You can run towards the skull!!
Ani!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuck!!
Oh!!
Stop, Okapi!!
Ha...!
Aaah!!
Ugh...!
...
Aaaaaa!!
Uuuuuuu!!
Ani!!
It's no good if you're alone!!
You'll be killed right away!!
For those with super large okapi...!!
Unpalatable…!
…Oi!!
Why...
why isn't my body moving...
Please move!
Everyone will die!
Liner...Peak...
Jean... Connie...
Mikasa... Ani.
Everyone is going to die!!
Wake up, you scum!!
Bastard!! Useless!!
Ugh... huh...
I hate myself! Zuuutt you!!
You have been betraying me!!
The life I received!! The expectations!! The responsibility too!!
Nothing!! Nothing!!
You couldn't give anything back!!
But!! Why is he dead?
Move!! Move!!
Aaaaaaa…!!
Aaaaaaa...!!
(People scream)
・～
(cry)
teeth….
・～
<Sand…｡・
Think about it...
if you're really dead...
How can you think without oxygen flowing to your brain ? >
<This is
not a dream, a vision, or an afterlife.>
<This is the “road”…
This is... reality!!>
<I'm supposed to be in the giant's mouth, so
why do I know everyone's situation...? ・
Is it because all Eldians
are connected through "roads"? ・
Then
maybe we can do something here...>
Yes, think about it...
Think!!
picture….
(Armin's footsteps)
Hello,
Mr. Zeke.
Ellen's friend.
Were you also
eaten by Ymir?
(Jeek) A long time ago...
When only matter existed in this world ...
(Jeek) Something imaginable and intangible
repeatedly appears and disappears.
Eventually, something survived.
It's called "life."
The reason why life remained in the end was...
This is because life
has the property of ``multiplying. ''
In order to increase, life changes its shape.
We have adapted to any environment and
have become what we are today.
More, wider, richer...
In other words, the purpose of life is to "increase."
This sand, stones, and water
are not going to increase.
However, life is still desperately trying to increase.
After all, death and species extinction go against the purpose of increasing numbers.
For that reason, there is a penalty called fear.
That child
was also desperately trying to escape from that pain...
Create a stronger, larger, and immortal body.
And to a world where even death doesn't exist...
She escaped...
That's the founder Ymir...
this is the "world where death doesn't exist"...
If that's the case,
what exactly is Ymir's purpose?
I also spend a lot of time here ...
I tried to understand her .
Even though I have this much power ...
I couldn't go against King Fritz
...
Stayed here for 2000 years
The reason I continued to follow King Fritz.
I'm sure I left something to be desired,
but...
Eren understood that, but
I couldn't...
That's why Ymir
joined Eren.
Please tell me
how to return to the outside world from here.
Well... I don't think it's possible anymore...
I'm not giving up on anything.
Why...
eh... That's...
Is it because it will still increase?
Is it really that important to you to keep the species alive ?
What's happening now...
This can be described as a tragic state of life ruled by fear .
brought about by completely meaningless
life activities.
Don't be afraid...
my friends are fighting!!
Because now we can still save many people
from fear...!!
I am fighting fear!!
Why can't I lose...?
Being alive means
you'll die someday, right?
Hmm…｡
Maybe I'll feel relieved before it's all over ...
I don't even know what it means...
After the days of being forced to dance just to increase ...
Now I'm free...
ah….
It was dusk, facing a tree on the hill...
The three of us raced...
Eren, who had just
started talking, suddenly started running...
Mikasa dared to run behind Eren...
I'm the dobe after all...
But... that day, the wind was warm and
it felt good just running...
There were a lot of dry leaves.
At that time, for some reason, I thought...
I think the three of us were born to play here together ...
Even when I'm reading a book at home on a rainy day...
Even when the squirrel ate the fruit I gave it...
That's what I thought when we all walked through the market...
I feel like this ordinary moment is so important...
it is…?
Hmm…｡
This one was buried in sand...
Why is that...
Now... But for me, this is...
It's not necessary or anything to increase
...
It's something very
important.
Ah... that's right.
Just throw it and catch it...
Throw it again. Just repeat it.
It doesn't make any sense...but it's true...
I
was happy just playing catch the whole time.
・
Peek!! Peak!!
Gah...!
If my arm heals,
I can still fight...!
It's the limit!! Back up to the bottom of the liner!
(Peak) is...!!
Liner!!
Oh...! ・
Jean!! Peak!!
Woo!!
Ani!!
Woo... woo...!
Coo...!
...!!
Ha, what...
Ugh... ugh...! ・
Porco!! Marcel!!
・
(Liner) Ymir!!
Did you help me...
B...Bertholdt...
I don't know...but...
Don't miss this opportunity!!
I got it!!
Armin!!
Give it back!!!
...Gaha!
Armin!!
Damn!!
Oooooooooooooooo!!
Ugh!!
Ani!!
Goho goho geho…｡
Kaha… gehogeho… ugh…｡
Annie...
Armin...
Sorry everyone...
But... it's okay now.
(Connie) Ani!! It’s behind you!!
・～
・
(Gabi) What do you mean?
A giant is helping you?
It seems so.
(Jeek) Ooi!!
Ooooo!!
...!!
Here it is!!
Eh...
that's stupid...
You wanted to meet me, right? Levi!!
I didn't want to meet you though!!
...Sieg.
(encourage)
(Connie) What's going on? This is...
It's all thanks to Sieg.
Sieg...
It awakened everyone who had been sleeping in the world of the road, where there is no life or death .
All Eldians
are connected by "roads".
That's probably...
This is because Founder Ymir
is seeking a connection.
Asking us something...
...!
Bertolt...
Kusava-san,
our wishes didn't come true...
I still think that the euthanasia plan was not a mistake...
But
if it's just to play catch with you...
I wonder if I can be born again...
that's why…·
I'd like to thank you, Dad.
I
took everything from you.
Life, power, and precious memories...
That's why I understand.
I can't stay still here .
everyone….
(Zeek Armin) Lend me your strength.
・～
Isn't it nice weather...
I wish I had thought of that sooner...
Well...
The bugs are too good to kill so many of them
...
The rumbling... has stopped...
Uaaaaaaa!!
Go!! Jean!!
Nu!! Argh!!
(Jean) Uuuuuuu!!
(Peak) Jean!!
Oh!!
this…!!
Hurrying to death... you stupid idiot!!
(explosion sound)
Argh!!
Grrrr…!!!!
This guy!! On Eren’s neck again!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuck!!
Liner!!
(Connie) Jean!! Peak!!・
Hurry and leave!!
Armin will blow away every bone!!
Wait!! Liner!!
(Peak) If it's an armored giant,
I'm sure it can withstand a super-sized explosion.
Above all, letting this opportunity pass
would mean ruining Reiner's resolve.
Nuaaaaaaaa!!!
thank you….
Without everyone's help...
I couldn't stop the rumbling...
Goodbye...
Eren.
(explosion sound)
Ugh...
(Gabi's father) Sister!! Are you okay?
What on earth...
・It was a huge explosion!!
・Did everyone survive?
(Father Falco)! that…!
(Jean) Look at the bones...!!・
Is Eren... dead?
Ugh!!
Ackerman awakens to his power...
Apparently , sudden headaches were
common...
I've been a slave who just follows orders...
ever since I was a kid...
Mikasa, I hated you.
Oh!
Oh...!!
・～
(Connie) That doesn't mean I don't have any regrets.・
but…·
We weren't wrong.
We stopped the rumbling...
How... from the containment area to here...
(Carina) Leonhart-
san led everyone to this point.
Let me go.
…Ha!
Armin!!
Where is Liner?
(Gabi) Reiner!!
(Jan) You're safe!!
Oi!! Look!! Over there!!
Are you still alive after that explosion?
Yes... what on earth is that?
Well...just...
It certainly shouldn't be kept alive.
(Explosion sound)
(Aluminum liner)!!
(explosion sound)
Well... I guess...
I don't think you'll die from that.
Ah...but what should I do?
...Eren.
(Earth rumbling)