That's bad!! If Eren comes into contact with the glowing thing,
the ground might start rumbling again...!!
(Connie) Oh, I have to kill him!!
How do you kill someone who survived that explosion?
The person you should aim for is Eren.
You understand...
this nightmare won't end until we kill him...
Dad, there's one last job left.
I'll do it for you, brother.
…why?
Why...
why does this happen?
Hah...
Did you hurt your leg?
Oh!
No, it was bad from the beginning...I was saved.
Can you walk?
(Leonhart)
If you hadn't shot all the bullets into the air...
We
would still be killing each other...
I've made enough mistakes...
Let 's work together
to get through this.Ah
...
(Ani) Dad
!!
Ha ha ha...
A...Ani?
(Gabi) This smoke is coming from that glowing thing!!
Did you die?
No... it smells like a dead giant.
Oh! this is…·
It's the same method as Ragako Village...
Oh!
…picture?
Mikasa!! Peak!! Get on Falco!!
Get out of here!!
What... what are you talking about?
Ackerman and those with the power of the Titans
are exceptions.
You should know best what to do !
That's... that's too much.
hurry up!!
No!! Dad!! Dad!!
Guaaaaaaaaaaaa...!!
Is this our last moment?
Well…｡・
I'll leave the rest to my friends,
because that's the end of the Survey Corps.
Do you remember, Jean? ・
About the night I burned the corpse.Ah
...
(Connie) It's all your fault, isn't it? ・
We were forced to save humanity...
Oh...!!
Idiot...
Is there something so... stupid like this?
(Onyankopon) Oi!! Oi!! Ani!!
Are you okay? What the hell happened?
(Roaring)
!!
Hey... Secretary!!
Ah...!!
Ugh...!
This guy...he called for the soldiers...
Just kidding!!
Never pass here!!
Wow!! Guooooo!!
Damn...! You really
like hell, Eren!!
It's okay... I
'll be with you till the end!!!
WOOOOOOOO!!
Connie... Jean... Gabi...!!
No way... why, mother...
Uggaaaa!!
(Liner)
Peak!! Ani!!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu!!
(Liner) We are...
How can I be rewarded?
Daaaa!! Uuuuu!!
(Levi) Mikasa・
Stay strong!!
We are the only ones who can kill Eren now!!
Ugh...!!
No more... no more...
Intolerable…!
I want to go home…!
I want to go back to our house...
Mikasa... wake up.
yeah….
I'm going to catch a cold.
Eren...?
that? I….
When did you fall asleep...
(Sound of chopping firewood)
I must have been really tired...
hmm...
I feel like I was having a long dream...
Let's just relax and do nothing today
.
I also managed to catch a big fish...
Mikasa...
Why are you crying?
…picture?
Why is that?
I... I wonder if it's okay to stay here ...
There's nothing I can do anymore...
picture?
Since that day when we left everything behind and
ran away here...
Two months have passed since Marley's war ended...
The war of invasion of Paradis Island is about to begin...
If we don't run, we'll all be killed...
Armin
is probably desperately looking for us too.
I have the ability to send Historia to hell and
kill each other for eternity.
Nor could they massacre people outside the island
...
In that case,
let's live the remaining four years of our lives quietly...
Just the two of us in a place where no one is around...
Mikasa, you were the one who said that .
Yeah….
I'm sorry...
I promised not to talk about this...
Can I make another promise?
If I die, please
throw away this muffler...
You're going to live a long time from now on...
Please forget about me and be free...
Please, Mikasa...
Forget it.
・～
sorry.
Can not.
Eren is in your mouth!!
Everyone cooperate!!
(Levi) Understood, Mikasa!!
(Falco) Oooooooo!!
Ellen!!!
Damn...!!
Dah!!
!! Doaaaa!!
Tee!!
・～
Take care.
Ellen.
・～
I know it 's for the sake of the future seen through the power of Attack on Titan,
but...
The reason you had to beat me up ...what?
Was it necessary to throw in a knee kick?
Desperate to push you away...
Even I was wondering what I was doing
...
Leave it to the momentum and flow...
It was really bad...
You should tell Mikasa that, not me.
You hurt me by saying such bullshit...
Ah... that's right.
Everything is
about us who were pushed away...
Defeat Eren
To make him into a hero who saved humanity from extinction ?
That's it.
You will be the benefactors of all surviving humans .
Although he was the "Island Devil",
he disobeyed Paradis Island and stuck to humanity.
He must become the most respected person in this world .
Well then,
like the Tiber family after the Great War...
Are you telling me to protect Paradis Island from the retaliation of humans outside the wall ?
There's no way we
can become heroes...
It's unfortunate, but me and everyone...
I'm not going to play the hero the way you want me to .
where….
That's where we wanted to go.
Let's talk while walking.
The story of the founder Ymir...
(Eren Armin) Haa...!
This is flaming water...
It really flows like a river...
How far
did you talk?
picture?
Because the founder Ymir has been following King Fritz for 2,000 years ...
The power of the Titans still exists...
That's right... My hometown was burned down, my parents were killed, and
my tongue was pulled out...
Even after gaining power equal to that of God,
he remained obedient...
I wonder what made her do that...
I touched her on the "road" and felt...
I couldn't believe it, but...
The founder Ymir... loved King Fritz.
…picture?
This is the true identity of what has continued to bind Ymir even after 2000 years .
It is impossible to understand the depths of founder Ymir's heart .
But... she was definitely in pain.
For 2,000 years,
I've been searching for someone to free me from my suffering...
It finally appeared.
That's Mikasa.
...Eh... I said Mikasa...
I said it. I guess you didn't hear me...
I heard you!
Why... Mikasa?
Well...
only the founder Ymir can understand...
I still
don't know what Mikasa will do...
What I knew for sure
was the result of Mikasa...
I kept going just to reach that result ...
Massacre humanity and
make them kill each other on Paradis Island.
Everyone... my precious friends...
I went into battle without knowing if I would survive .
That's the future I saw at the medal award ceremony...
Armin...
My head
is messed up...
The influence of the founder's power is...
There is no past and no future, they exist at the same time...
So... I had no choice...
That day... that time...
Bertholdt
shouldn't have died yet...
…picture?
So I missed it...
What led me to...
Let's go, Ellen.
…Ahh.
So... what were you thinking?
what?
It's about Mikasa.
Do you think you can forget about Eren and
live happily with someone else?
As you wish.
Well, I don't know.
Good...! Huh… hah…!
Ha... ha...｡
...It hurts.
You don't understand,
I don't remember forgiving you!!
What do you think about Mikasa's love for you
?
To Mikasa, who has risked her life
to only look at Eren...
Do you think you can just forget about me ?
At least Mikasa
can forget about making this woman cry...
You should be happy!!
Well, I feel like I'll be able to find a good person sooner than I expected and get along easily...
No...
Huh?
I don't want that!! I
can't believe Mikasa has a man!!
I want you to think only of me for the rest of your life!!
Even after I die...
I hope it lasts for more than 10 years!!
Huh… eh…｡
Ah... that's right...
To say something so... uncool...
Please don't tell Mikasa about this...
I want you to be happy... really...
But… ah…｡
Damn it...!
I don't want to die...
I want to be with Mikasa and everyone...
Ellen! Let's search without giving up!!
Isn't there another way...!
No!!
I'm sure everyone , just like me,
didn't want to die...
But... I...
...!
It's 80%
...huh?
They trampled 80% of humanity to death...
What a...
thing...!!
Eren!! Why!!
I am literally
trying to complete the eradication of humanity outside the wall.
You will be blocked.
The result is 80%...
The world outside the wall
will fall to the same level of civilization as Paradis Island.
In other words... it probably won't be a unilateral war of retaliation
...
This fight will never end.
Huh, hah, hah...
What is that...
Are you trying to say that what we did was in vain?
That's okay!!
Stop the massacre that hasn't happened yet!!
You can't...
you can save up to 20% of humanity.
It's already decided...
Has it been decided...?
You decided to kill yourself, right?
I've tried so many times and been disappointed, but ...
The memories of the future
will remain exactly the same...
Armin... as you said...
I am...a free slave.
Uh… ugh…!
What a stupid thing!!
It's already...!! Is there no way to take it back?
This is impossible!!
This is not a solution!!
There would be no war without people...
Is there anyone who would take such a joke seriously?
Ellen...
It's true that this battle has no end in sight...
The hell we experienced
was repeated over and over again...I'm sure...
Still...someday...
I'm sure someday
we'll understand each other...
Even a small wish ...
No one believes me anymore...
The only lesson left is...
kill or be killed... That's it...
Are you saying that you did everything for us ?
(Grisha) "Eren"... That's your name.
No, that's not true...
Eren... you're free...
I... I wanted it to be flat...
I wanted to see this view...
…why?
I don't know why, but...
I wanted to do it... I really wanted to...
I thought it was all to protect you ...
But... Sasha and Hanji both
died because of me.
I ended up having them kill each other with Flock and the others
...
Why... why did this happen...
I finally understood.
It's because you're an idiot.
An ordinary idiot who can be found anywhere
has acquired power...
That's why I couldn't help but end up like this ...
Isn't that what it means?
I understand...
!
I have also had times when I wanted to erase people from this world .
Liar...
that's why you think that...
No one would think so.
Because he is a hero who saved 20% of humanity...
But... I was the one who showed Ellen the books about the outside world .
I was the one who made Eren imagine a free world without anyone .
it is?
I guess you finally noticed...
even though it was always there at your feet...
Because I'm always looking far away...
Thank you Ellen.
You showed me this scenery on the other side of the wall ...
This is what we did.
So... from now on, we'll be together forever...
from now? …where?
If only... in hell.
I will suffer for the crime of killing 80% of humanity .
Two people.
・～
Armin... it's time.
I'll erase the memories I spent here...
I'll remember it again when it's all over...
Ah... next time we'll kill each other...
And the next time we meet...
Ahh….
I'll be waiting for you... in hell.
Yeah….
We'll be together forever...
(Ani) Has your injury healed yet?
that…? Annie...?
Yeah...because I had time.
I remembered... this...
...Armin
!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...!!
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...!!
Armin also regained his memory, right?
When Ellen came to see us...
Ah... I heard...
The result of Mikasa's choices...
The power of the Titans
will be erased from this world...
I remember... you polite idiot.
Eren... you're that guy...
Eren says...
Mom said she'll turn back into a human too...
He...
told us... to live long...
Are you...?
It's an unnecessary burden for you, you
bastard who is in a hurry to die...
yes….
I wanted to talk to you too...
welcome home.
Right now... Dad.
Gabbyiiiiii!!
Hey you guys.
Were you watching?
This seems to be the ending.
You all gave... your heart...
・～
(Connie) Sasha…｡
father, mother…!
Ah... Gabi...｡
(Falco) Gabiiii!!
Gabbyiiiiii!!
Falco!!
・～
mother….
I...
it's like I'm not an armored giant anymore...
(Karina)
...Is it true?
That was good...
!
I'm sorry for all this time... Reiner...
I didn't need anything more .
Oh...!
Already... let's go.
picture…? where?
If I stay here like this, Eren will surely...
I can't give him a proper burial.
…I agree.
Let me sleep in a quiet place...
Eren always fell asleep there.
Yes, I think it's a good place.
・～
(Leon Hart) Listen, Secretary Mueller!
Eren Jaeger is dead!
Even the power of the giant disappeared from this world...! ・
We are just people now!
Can you prove it? Now here.
If it's a blood test...
(Muller) Right here and now!!
Please... prove it.・
Is it a human... or a giant...
If we still have the power of the Titans,
we will use our strength to resist.
However, even now that a gun is pointed at you,
you remain helpless...
This is proof that we are human beings.
you…?
Armin Arlert, Eldian of Paradis Island .
He is the one who killed Eren Jaeger from Attack on Titan .
It was you...
The one who was looking inside my head...
I think your love was a long nightmare...
The lives that were taken will never come back.
nevertheless…·
I exist because you created a life for me .
・～
Good night, Ymir.
(Histria) <Three years have passed since that day, which was called the "Battle of Heaven and Earth"
...
An incredible number of lives have been taken.
Those who survived
may also suffer from scars that never heal.
<As the world in the midst of loss fears,
the country of Eldia...
Formed an "army" controlled by the Jaeger faction .
I am getting stronger day by day.・
Fearing retribution from the surviving humans on the other side of the ocean ...
The island will come together and raise its voice.・
If you win, you live; if you lose, you die.・
if you do not fight, you can not win.·
Fight, fight.・
Even if the giants disappear,
the conflict will not end.・
Eren
told me about the future as far as he knew.
Even if I can't see any further into the future ...
I could clearly see this future .・
I'm sure this result
wasn't just Eren's choice.・
This world is the result of our choices .
We have to fight.・
In order not to fight any more...
Even if I have to live my days without peace again .・
It's not the life he wanted for us ...
Whether he wanted it or not,
it was entrusted to us.・
How to live the remaining grace...>
"A world without giants."
No matter how many times I look at it, Historia's handwriting is beautiful.
It also smells good...
(Jan) I've said it many times, but
stop feeling bad about married people. It's disgusting.
It seems like Jean is worried about his hair and
can't help it.
Who are you going to show it to?
For female students reading history textbooks.
Are you confusing this with a picture book about horses?
(Jan)
It's a shame that your lifespan has been extended, Reiner.
・(Sound of door opening)
Paradis Island is now in sight.
Armin: Do you really think it'll work out?
Destroy the wall, betray the island...
The people who killed Eren, who are worshiped by the people of Eldia ...
Serving as ambassador for the Allied powers in peace negotiations...
I don't think I would be surprised if it was sunk around here
...
Ah... I can't believe the ship is still
floating...
This is the role of the world's hero that that idiot forced upon me .
What do you want to live longer?
What, Annie , did you just board the ship with the intention of returning home alive ?
No way, but you guys...
You didn't come here to commit suicide,
right?
The answer is that I'm headed to hell again .
The Survey Corps
are dreamers and don't give up easily.
I'm a military police officer.
For now, I'm not killed yet.
Everyone on Paradis Island
should want to know.
Our story.
・～
People who killed each other a lot...
Why did it appear on Paradis Island...
Are you appealing for peace?
・～
The story we saw...
Let's talk about it all.
・～
Ellen... everyone will be coming to see you soon.
Are you happy?
・～
Huh… ugh…｡
Uh... huh...｡
Huh... uh...｡
Huh... huh...｡
(cry)
I want to see you again….
(Sound of wings)
!!
・～
Ellen...
Thank you for wrapping the muffler...
・～
・“Time brought [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]
Calm days [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]”
・"Like a flower in your hand [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]"
・"Hidden words [Out: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]
die without telling anyone [Out: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]"
≪Requiem of the night that repeats≫
・" The flowers you loved on the coffin "
・"If you want to forgive your sins,
let the dawn shine"
・“Be fruitful and multiply,
fill the earth”
・`` I released the steel bird into the sky.''
・“Freedom
becomes a crimson bow and arrow.”
・"Repeat over and over again"
・“ I can’t throw away the stone I was throwing back .”
・"The sky that cowardly humans looked up at"
・"A bow and arrow of the underworld that resembles a meteor"
・"History repeats itself"
・“And then it becomes ≪Nothing≫ again.”
・"Can you hear me? Get out of here [Outside: 9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]"
・“No matter how many times I get lost [Outside:9BEF8D51305948236CD4F6198973DBB9]”
・"Plants have sprouted even in the burnt out fields."
・"The shadow and light of civilization"
・"In the cave of the great tree where I watched everything"
・"What do you know?"